Diego Garzón.

Software Developer | Web Developer | Frontend | Backend bogotá, colombia

+57 3195327114 · +57 3011049252

<u>diegogarzon357@gmail.com</u> • <u>https://github.com/DiegoGarzon11</u> <u>https://diegogarzon.netlify.app</u> • <u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/diego-garzon-b20771204/</u>

WORK EXPERINCE

Quickcomm, Perú

(August 2022 – nowadays)

I am the person who is in charge of the new version of the company software. Consuming the company's API to later use this data, when needed, and display it in the different components

In addition to this, the page must be very user-friendly (ux - ui) that's why everything is built with material ui and tailwind for a more user-friendly interface.

Of course when doing these tasks there are errors and different obstacles, I am in charge of looking for the best solutions for this

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Self-taught fullStack web developer with +2 years of experience and knowledge in the most used technologies in the industry, currently i'm more focused in Frontend

I am able to solve the problems that I encounter, and investigate in depth, I like to be updated, learn different technologies, that help me expand in this amazing world of development

My technologies are HTML, CSS, tailwind, JavaScript, TypeScript, Node.js, Express, ReactJS, Angular, MySQL, Sequelize, JWT, Unit Test (mocha, jest, chai), Git, GitHub, Template engine Ejs, API REST, Agile methodologies (Scrum), i love all ecosystem of JavaScript.

ACHIEVEMENTS

- I have improved the optimization of different websites, and I have made them more user-friendly.
- I am able to analyze future errors, and look for previous solutions and choose the best one to avoid future conflicts.

- Additionally, I have found better ways to perform different tasks.
- Every day I exceed my limits in development, analyze the problems I encounter and find the best way to solve them.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Digital house project

(2021 - 2022)

Worked on an e-commerce web page in frontend and backend optimizing and improving the user experience using everything technologies in my professional summary this was in a team of 4 developers.

Main personal project

(2022 - 2022)

I've been working on a web application where you can add, modify and delete your favorites movies this was made with JavaScript, Node.js, Express, Html, Css, bootstrap and this's in process to link up to database Formation

Soft Skills

- Self-learning
- Skill to develop
- Logical thoughts and reasoning
- Good communication and listening
- Quick adaptation
- Good predisposition to work in a team or individually
- Imagination, creativity, and taste for visual aesthetics
- Professionalism and responsibility
- Creation of websites

Skills

- Maintenance and error resolution
- Implement good practices in development (responsive, UX-UI)
- Management of user interactions and interface animations
- Management of asynchronous connections with Ajax and/or fetch.
- Implementation of validations in JavaScript for forms
- Use of Session and Cookies to store information.

- Planning and estimation of the development of the Web server
- Analysis, design, and implementation of a database system
- Collaborate with Frontend developers
- Collaborate with Backenddevelopers

Languages

Spanish: Native Language

English: Upper Intermediate

French: Basic

ACADEMIC TRAINING

Digital house - Argentina

(2021 - 2022)

Web developer - Fullstack